我们目前有我们所有的功能要查找
we currently have all of our functions to find
在单个模块中
in a single module
和
and
我们已经相当自律地分组在一起
we've been fairly disciplined about grouping together
有类似问题的函数
functions that have similar concerns
但我们从经验中知道
but we know from experience
拥有它们
that having them all
在一个模块中会变得有点不守规矩
in one module is going to become a bit unruly
是的，在这个模块中已经有点疯狂了
yeah it's getting a bit wild already in this one module
但我们通常从一个模块中的所有内容开始
but we generally start with everything in one module
然后一旦我们看到类似功能的集群
and then once we see clusters of similar functions
好
well
然后我们将它们组织在一个正确命名的模块中
then we'll organize those in a properly named module
所以让我们做一些功能争论
so let's do some function wrangling
在我们的管道中
in our pipeline
我们有一些我们插入的功能
we have some functions that we plug in
映射某些请求和响应，然后
to map certain requests and responses and then
以各种方式修改对话
modify the conversation in various ways
所以例如我们有重写路径日志然后跟踪
so for example we have rewrite path log and then track
我们想把它们放在一个新模块中
we want to put those in a new module
所以我只是要删掉那些的定义
so I'm just going to cut out the definitions of those
功能就在这里
functions right here
然后在顶部我要定义一个新模块
and then at the top I'm going to define a new module
命名是
naming is
始终是创建新模块最困难的部分
always the hardest part of creating a new module
让我们称之为插件
let's just call this plugins
这将是服务插件
it's going to be service plugins
一个elixir文件可以定义多个模块
and a single elixir file can define multiple module
所以我们只是要把这些模块放在同一个
so we're just going to put these modules in the same
文件现在不要让这个点字符把你扔到这里
file now don't let this dot character throw you here
当我第一次看到这样的模块命名方案时
when I first saw this module naming scheme like this
我认为它暗示了一些等级关系
I assumed it implied some hierarchical relationship
在调查模块和插件模块之间
between the survey module and the plugins module
但实际上并没有隐含的关系
but in fact there is no implied relationship
所有模块均已定义
all modules are defined
在顶层
at the top level
使用点只是给我们一个简单方便的方法
using dots just gives us a simple convenient way
表达一个名字空间
to express a name space
现在我的复制粘贴缓冲区中有这些功能
now I've got those functions in my copy paste buffer
所以我要
so I'm just going to
像这样粘贴模块内部
paste those inside of the module like that
然后我们可以关闭
and then we can close
这是崇高的
this up in sublime
只是给我们多一点空间
just to give us a little bit more room
我说模块充当名称
I said that the module acts as a name
空间调用函数
space so to call the functions
我们需要使用模块名称
we need to use the module name
所以当我们调用重写路径时，我们不得不说调查
so when we call rewrite path we have to say survey
插件重写路径
plugins rewrite path
调用 log 之前的方法相同
the same way before calling log
我们必须在它前面加上模块名称
we have to prefix it with the module name
和轨道一样的东西
and the same thing for track
如果我们把它保存起来
if we save this away
看起来我们没有破坏任何东西
and it looks like we haven't broken anything
用模块名称作为函数名称的前缀是
prefixing the function names with the module names is
然而明确的
explicit however
模块名称可能会变得相当长
module names can get fairly long
而且之前输入模块的名称很繁琐
and it's tedious to type the name of the module before
每个函数名
every function name
幸运的是，有几个选项可以解决这个问题
thankfully there's a couple options to deal with this
一种方法是导入模块
one approach is to import the module
要做到这一点，我们只是在函数之上
to do that we just go up above the function
在模块的顶层，我们说导入
at the top level of the module and we say import
调查插件
survey plugins
这将导入这些功能
and that's going to import those functions
进入当前名称空间
into the current name space
调查处理程序名称空间
the survey handler name space
所以现在我们可以摆脱
so now we can get rid of
所有这些功能的这个前缀在这里
this prefix on all these functions here
如果我们把它保存好，那也应该有用
if we save that away well that should work too
但是以这种方式导入函数有点随意
however importing functions this way is a bit cavalier
因为它导入了所有功能
because it imports all the functions
这可能会导致歧义
which can lead to ambiguity
现在在这种情况下这没什么大不了的
now it's not a big deal in this case
因为我们只处理少数几个函数
because we're only dealing with a handful of functions
但不是导入整个模块
but instead of importing the entire module
我们可以更有选择性
we could be more selective and
只导入我们需要的功能
only import the functions we need
我们只使用选项来做到这一点
and we do that by using the option only
然后我们给它一个列表，我们可以说
and then we give it a list and we can say
好的，我们想要重写
okay we want the rewrite
接受一个参数的路径函数
path function that takes one argument
我们还想要接受一个参数的 log 函数
we also want the log function that takes one argument
以及带有一个参数的 track 函数
and the track function that takes one argument
这样做只会让它更明确
and doing it this way just makes it more explicit
定义这些功能的地方
where those functions are defined
注意这里的数字
note here that the number
是函数
is the functions airily
或它需要的参数数量
or the number of arguments it takes
这不是具有该名称的函数的数量
it's not the number of functions with that name
所以这会导入我们所有的五个函数
so this imports all five of our functions
我们把它存起来
we save that away
很好，它也很好用
well it works just as well
现在我们开始说我们不想要我们所有的
now we started by saying we didn't want all of our
一个模块中的功能
functions in one module
并且以同样的方式
and in the same way
我们不希望我们所有的模块都在一个文件中
we don't want all of our modules in one file
事实证明这非常容易做到
and it turns out it's super easy to do
所以让我们删掉插件模块
so let's cut the plugins module
我们会把它放在一个单独的文件中
and we'll put it in a separate file
我要在这里打开侧边栏
I'm going to open up the sidebar here
在我们的 lib 调查目录中
and in our lib survey directory
我们将创建一个新文件，我们将其称为插件
we'll just create a new file and we'll call it plugins
前任
ex
然后我将粘贴到该模块中
and then I'll just paste in that module
现在如果我们把它存起来，我也
now if we save that away and I also
保存处理程序前
save handler ex
我尝试以崇高的方式运行它
and I try to run this in sublime
我们从哪里得到这个空气模块
where we get this air module
服务插件未加载并且
service plugins is not loaded and
找不到
could not be found
以同样的方式
in the same way
如果我们在顶层的命令行上结束
if we're over on a command line in our top level
调查目录
survey directory
我们尝试在我们的处理程序上运行 elixir 命令
and we try to run the elixir command on our handler
ex 文件很好，我们得到了同样的错误，它找不到
ex file well we get this same error it can't find
调查插件
survey plugins
那是因为在任何一种情况下它都没有
and that's because in either case it doesn't have
代码路径设置
the code path setup
对于混合项目
for a mixed project
所以此时我们需要将它作为一个混合应用程序运行
so at this point we need to run it as a mix application
为此，我们将启动修复
and to do that we're going to fire up fix
但我们会这样做
but we're going to do it
在我们的应用程序中
in the context of our application
通过使用性破折号大写 s 和混合
by using sex dash capital s and mix
然后它继续
and then it went ahead
并编译并加载了我们项目中的所有模块
and compiled and loaded all the modules in our project
然后它解释模块之外的任何代码
and then it interpreted any code outside of a module
所以我们看到了和以前一样的输出
so we see the same output we used to see
在崇高的构建窗口中
in the sublime build window
它只是打印出结果
it's just printing out the results of
通过我们的处理程序运行我们的请求
running our request through our handler
如果我们想重新编译并
and if we want to recompile and
重新加载调查模块
reload the survey module
好吧，我们总是可以使用 r 辅助函数
well we can always use the r helper functions
我们只说r
we just say r
服务处理程序
servi handler
所以它重新编译了模块并重新加载了它
so it recompiled the module and reloaded it
和
and
还解释了模块之外的代码
also interpreted the code that's outside of the module
所以这是我们运行处理程序模块的一种方式
so this is a way for us to run our handler module
当我们在做的时候
while we're at it
解析功能确实有宾至如归的感觉
the parse function does a necessarily feel at home
生活在处理程序模块中
living in the handler module
所以让我们来看看 parse 函数
so let's take the parse function
我们将创建一个新的解析器 ex 文件
and we'll create a new parser ex file
然后我们将定义一个模块调查解析器
and then we'll define a module survey parser
我们将把我们的 parse 函数粘贴进去
and we'll paste our parse function into it
然后回到我们的处理程序中，我们需要导入它
then back in our handler we need to import that
所以在这里我们需要导入它
so up here we need to import it
就像我们对插件所做的那样
just like we did with plugins
我要说进口
I'm going to say import
见解析器
see parser
它只有一个功能
and it only has one function
它被称为解析，能力为一
it's called parse with an ability of one
现在回到九点多
now back over nine
例如，如果我们尝试像以前那样重新编译处理程序模块
ex if we try to recompile our handler module as we did
在我们得到这个熟悉的错误模块之前
before while we get this familiar error module
服务解析器未加载且找不到
service parser is not loaded and could not be found
因为它不知道解析器模块
because it doesn't know about the parser module
所以此时我们可以重新启动性爱会话
so at this point we can either restart the sex session
或者我们可以重新编译整个应用程序
or we can recompile the entire application
使用重新编译
using recompile
这是一个辅助功能
that's a helper function
它不需要任何论据，但是
it doesn't take any arguments but
你需要使用括号
you need to use parentheses
否则你会在那里收到警告
otherwise you'll get a warning there
它重新编译应用程序，我们得到
and it recompile the application and we get the
我们的处理程序熟悉的输出
familiar output from our handler
接下来我们将定义
coming up we'll define
另一个恰好是长生不老药结构的模块
another module that happens to be an elixir structure
并使用另一种技术来引用模块
and use another technique to reference modules
别名
the alias